arwebzone.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy

At arwebzone.com we consider the privacy of our visitors extremely important. This privacy policy document describes the types and use of personal information that is collected and recorded by ARWebZone.

**Log Files**  
ARWebZone makes use of log files that contain information related to  IP addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze user interest, administer the site,  and gather demographic information. This helps us to improve our website. IP address and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on arwebzone.com.  
→  Use of DART cookie enables Google to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to ARWebZone.COM and other websites on the Internet.  
→ Our visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Our Advertising Partners**

Google is our advertising partner and they may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

_While Google as our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site.  
_

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on arwebzone.com and which are sent directly to user’s browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to note the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns.

ARWebZone has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**3rd Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these 3rd party ads servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of other advertisers or websites.

**Consent**  
By visiting ARWebZone.COM , you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

If you need more information or have any questions related to our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://arwebzone.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

**Update**  
Our Privacy Policy was last updated on: Sunday, June 30th, 2013.
